JOSEPH SHARICK

Holtwood, PA 17532 | 7175756318 | jsharick7@gmail.com

Portfolio - https://joe-sharick.netlify.app/ https://github.com/Jsharick7 https://www.linkedin.com/in/joseph-sharick-51085674/

Professional Summary

Self-motivated, enthusiastic professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on quality results. Proven experience developing responsive web applications using industry-standard languages and libraries. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Energized by encountering new projects with a desire to understand them and grow as a developer.

Skills

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React, Node.js, MongoDB, SQL, AJAX, Git
- Database Management
- Microsoft Office
- Process Improvement
- Software best practices and principles

- Customer Service
- Problem Solving/Troubleshooting
- Communication—Verbal, Written
- Creative Collaboration
- Self-directed learning

Work History

Game Developer

01/2019 to 04/2020

Elected Games Studios – Lancaster, PA

- Drove development of unique mobile-based games in Unity/C# engine through data organization, game logic, and sound production.
- Created prototypes based upon design concepts.
- Managed user profiles by implementing Google Play API into applications.
- Followed specifications and technical limitations when designing to meet established design and gameplay objectives.

Adjunct Professor of Piano and Keyboard Studies

01/2018 to 05/2020

Lancaster Bible College – Lancaster, PA

- Maintained great communication with Dept. Chair, colleagues, and students to ensure quality of class environment and student interaction.
- Managed weekly appointments for 25+ individual lessons per week.
- Achieved standards set by National Association of Schools of Music through revising class curriculum for 3 undergraduate level courses.

Service Manager

06/2014 to 05/2016

Chipotle Mexican Grill - Lancaster, PA

- Handled inventory flow and responsible cash management.
- Trained 30+ less-skilled service workers on standards, efficiency and conflict resolution for best-inclass customer service.
- Oversaw implementation of customer rewards campaigns.
- Efficiently assisted crew with problematic transactions to maintain customer satisfaction.
- Maintained team productivity by leading high-energy environment.
- Planned and implemented safety protocols and equipment performance standards.

Education

Responsive Web Design Certification 2020 FreeCodeCamp.org

- Continuing Education in Web Development.
- Coursework in developing projects using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, and React.

Complete 2019 Web Development Bootcamp Udemy

2019

 Coursework in HTML and UI Design, server storage, APIs, OAuth/security, and templating technologies.

Master's of Music: Piano Pedagogy

05/2019

West Chester University of Pennsylvania - West Chester, PA

- Achieved audition-based graduate assistantship.
- Graduated with 3.91 GPA.

Bachelor's of Music: Piano Performance **Lancaster Bible College** - Lancaster, PA

05/2014

• Graduated with honors.